[{
    "type": "mcq",
	"question": "Calculate the volume necessary to provide 20mg of Ranitidine IV from a 25mg/ml vial.",
	"choices": ["a", "b", "c", "d"],
	"answer": ["0.8ml", "0.6ml", "0.4ml", "1.25ml"],
	"correct": "a"
},
{
    "type": "mcq",
	"question": "How much of hyocine-N-buthylcromide (Buscopan) 20mg/ml should be drawn out to get 15mg?",
	"choices": ["a", "b", "c", "d"],
	"answer": ["1ml", "0.25ml", "0.5ml", "0.75ml"],
	"correct": "a"
},
{
    "type": "mcq",
	"question": "An order is received for Augmentin syrup 228mg BD for 10 days. How many bottles of Augmentin that you need to supply? (Volume of one bottle of Augmentin 228/5ml is 70ml)",
	"choices": ["a", "b", "c", "d"],
	"answer": ["1 bottle", "2 bottles", "3 bottles", "4 bottles"],
	"correct": "a"
},
{
    "type": "mcq",
	"question": "The usual dose of chloropheniramine for children<12 years is 0.35mg/kg/day. How much should a 20kg child take each time if he has to take the medication 3 times daily?",
	"choices": ["a", "b", "c", "d"],
	"answer": ["1mg", "2mg", "2.3mg", "7mg"],
	"correct": "a"
},
{
    "type": "mcq",
	"question": "Patient came with prescription for Lantus Solostar with instruction of 6 units ON for 90 days. How many pens of Solostar would you need to supply? (Each pen contain 300 units with an expiry of 4 weeks after opening)",
	"choices": ["a", "b", "c", "d"],
	"answer": ["1 pen", "2 pen", "3 pen", "4 pen"],
	"correct": "a"
},
{
    "type": "short",
	"question": "Digoxin 62.5mcg can also be written as __mg.",
	"choices": [],
	"answer": [],
	"correct": ""
},
{
    "type": "short",
	"question": "Match the generic names below with their brand names",
	"choices": ["Rosuvastatin", "Chlorpheniramine", "Frusemide", "Metformin", "Mefenamic Acid", "Isomeprazole"],
	"answer": ["Glucophage", "Nexium", "Lasix", "Crestor", "Ponstan", "Piriton"],
	"correct": "a"
},
{
    "type": "short",
	"question": "Write down the possible indications for the following",
	"choices": ["Enalapril", "Aspirin", "Lorazepam", "Hydroxyzine", "Omeprazole", "Isosorbide Mononitrate"],
	"answer": ["", "", "", "", "", ""],
	"correct": ""
},
{
    "type": "short",
	"question": "Write down the generic names for the following drugs",
	"choices": ["Celebrex", "Span K", "Klacid", "Zocor", "Norvasc"],
	"answer": ["", "", "", "", ""],
	"correct": ""
},
{
    "type": "short",
	"question": "What is the maximum dose of paracetamol tablet for an adult?",
	"choices": "",
	"answer": "",
	"correct": ""
},
{
    "type": "mcq",
	"question": "Which of the following is NOT a correct dosage for diclofenac",
	"choices": ["a", "b", "c"],
	"answer": ["50mg BD", "75mg SR TDS PRN", "25mg every 6 to 8 hourly PRN"],
	"correct": ""
},
{
    "type": "mcq",
	"question": "Statins such as simvastatin and lovastatin are to be taken at night",
	"choices": ["True", "False"],
	"answer": ["True", "False"],
	"correct": ""
},
{
    "type": "short",
	"question": "What is the maximum dose of paracetamol tablet for an adult?",
	"choices": "",
	"answer": "",
	"correct": ""
}]